Welcome to our intro to business reports.
Your Amazon Seller Central account gives you access to a number of business reports.
You can use them to help identify sales trends, recognize your top performing products, and discover
new opportunities to grow your business.
To access your business reports, select the menu icon in the top left corner of Seller Central.
Hover over reports and select business reports.
You'll arrive at the sales dashboard page, which provides a summary of your sales metrics.
Use this information to identify trends and act quickly.
The sales snapshot section displays your current sales and order performance.
Use the compare sales section to compare these numbers to your sales and order performance from
yesterday, the same day last week, and the same day last year.
Customize these views by selecting a custom date range, specific category, or fulfillment method.
Then click apply to update the page.
You can also filter by selecting the checkboxes in the compare sales section and toggle between
graph view and table view.
Your sales snapshot is refreshed about once per hour, so check back regularly.
On the left side of the sales dashboard page, you'll see a number of business reports arranged by
date, ASIN, and other categories.
Click a report name to open it.
We recommend starting with the detail page, sales, and traffic by child item report.
This includes information on the performance of your products and each of their variations.
If your product has variations, that product is considered the parent item and its variations are
considered its child items.
For example, if you sell a shirt in different sizes and colors, the shirt represents the parent
item.
The shirt's variations, such as blue and medium, represent child items.
The detail page, sales, and traffic by child item report is organized by child items, so you can
compare how unique variations of the same product are performing.
The default time frame for this report is one month, but you can choose a specific date range you'd
like to review instead.
There are many ways to interact with the report to help inform your business strategies.
We recommend the following.
Sort the ordered product sales column in descending order to see which product variations have the
most unit sales.
Sort the ordered product sales column in ascending order to see which product variations have the
least unit sales.
Sort the page views column in ascending order to see which of your items customers find most often,
or in descending order to see which they find least often.
If an item isn't selling well but has a high number of page views, we recommend pricing the product
more competitively.
If page views are low, you might benefit from promoting the product with a coupon or a sponsored
products campaign.
Note that this and other business reports don't automatically factor in returns or refunds.
Click Show Hide Columns and select the checkboxes next to Units Refunded, Refund Rate, and Claims
Amount.
Then select Save Columns to show these values.
As with the sales dashboard, you can also modify the report to show a custom date range.
Bookmark the page in your browser or copy and paste the URL into your personal notes to save the
report parameters you selected.
If you'd like to download this or other business reports, select download.
csv at the top of the reports page.
For more information on the metrics included in the Detail Page Sales and Traffic by Child Item
Report, select Learn More at the top of the page or click Column Titles.
We also recommend using the Sales and Traffic and Seller Performance business reports.
You can use the Sales and Traffic Report to review your daily sales metrics on a line graph or in
a detailed table.
Each of the table's columns include an icon that reveals a drop-down list when clicked.
Click the icon to remove a metric from your report, add a metric to the line graph, or read a brief
description of what it measures.
The Seller Performance report helps you understand customer satisfaction.
Here are a few of the metrics in this report.
The Refund Rate metric shows you what percentage of your orders are being returned or refunded.
The received negative feedback rate metric calculates the percentage of your orders that received
negative feedback on the day listed in the date column.
Finally, the By Week and By Month metrics allow you to view customer satisfaction information received
within those timeframes.
You can also select custom dates for the report.
This concludes our Intro to Business reports.
As a next step, we recommend customizing your reports and determining which reports, metrics, and
timeframes work best for your business.
Thank you and happy selling in the Amazon Store!